#!/usr/bin/python3

#Dictionay of questions
quiz = {
        "Q1" : "question" : "What is War Machine's first name?",
               "answer":"james"
        },  
        "Q2" : "question" : "What country is the scarlet witch from?",
			   "answer" : "sokovia"
        },
        "Q3" : "question" : "What is the first name of Tony Stark's daughter?",
               "answer" : "morgan"
        },
        "Q4" : "question" : "Peter Quill's father is considered what type of being?",
               "answer" : "Cellestial"
        },
        "Q5" : "question" : "What was the acronym for the agency that imprisoned Loki?",
               "answer" : "TVA"
        },
        "Q6" : "question" : "What city was Steve Roger's from",
               "answer" : "brooklyn"
        },
        "Q7" : "question" : "What type of doctor is Michael Morbius?",
               "answer" : "biochemist"
        },
        "Q8" : "question" : "On what planet does the soul stone reside?",
               "answer" : "volmir"
        },
        "Q9" : "question" : "What fruit is Pepper Potts allergic to?",
               "answer" : "strawberries"
        ,
        "Q10" : "question" : "What is the Winter Soldiers middle name?",
                "answer" : "buchanan"
        }
}  
